<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss xmlns:sparkle="http://www.andymatuschak.org/xml-namespaces/sparkle" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>recipe-robot</title>
    <description>Most recent changes with links to updates.</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>2.4.0</title>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 19:10:49 -0700</pubDate>
      <sparkle:version>1471</sparkle:version>
      <sparkle:shortVersionString>2.4.0</sparkle:shortVersionString>
      <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>11.0</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
      <description><![CDATA[<h3>Fixed</h3>
<ul>
<li>Fixed issue with app description parsing that was causing most descriptions to show "Popular multimedia player."</li>
<li>Fixed redundant versioning caused by Recipe Robot's treatment of Sparkle feeds being out of date with SparkleUpdateInfoProvider (#207).</li>
<li>Restored icon extraction when Jamf recipes (but not Munki) are selected in user preferences (#203).</li>
<li>Fixed an EOFError that could happen if the <code>RecipeCreateLocation</code> doesn't exist. (#185).</li>
</ul>
<h3>Changed</h3>
<ul>
<li>Updated app to use latest version of Sparkle self-updater framework.</li>
<li>Converted Python tests from nose to unittest and configured for code coverage.</li>
<li>Made functional tests optional during unittest runs. Specify <code>RUN_FUNCTIONAL_TESTS=true</code> to include them.</li>
<li>Built out Swift unit testing for the Mac app.</li>
<li>Improved company suffix stripping (e.g. Inc, LLC, Ltd) and included s.r.o. suffix.</li>
<li>Updated Python syntax to 3.10 using <code>pyupgrade</code>.</li>
<li>Added <code>s.r.o.</code> to corporate suffixes able to be removed.</li>
<li>Data structure adjustments to recipe generation functions.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Removed</h3>
<ul>
<li>Removed support for pulling app descriptions from now-inoperative Informer site</li>
</ul>]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://github.com/homebysix/recipe-robot/releases/download/v2.4.0/RecipeRobot-2.4.0.dmg" length="4348387" type="application/octet-stream" sparkle:edSignature="KlVb+AQC2lSL+HwC6nlgAYTZCe9ByuRgs40O8/LvdnitUBdx24gf+vo5D4T3y9c7yT0d6q2ZZspP/CCh/5ZcCw=="/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recipe Robot 2.3.2</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2025 15:21:29 -0800</pubDate>
      <sparkle:version>1407</sparkle:version>
      <sparkle:shortVersionString>2.3.2</sparkle:shortVersionString>
      <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>11.0</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
      <description><![CDATA[<h3>Fixed</h3>
<ul>
<li>Resolved an issue with Sparkle feed parsing that could cause Recipe Robot to insert a static download URL in URLDownloader if the feed provided a version at the item level instead of the enclosure level (#206).</li>
</ul>]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://github.com/homebysix/recipe-robot/releases/download/v2.3.2/RecipeRobot-2.3.2.dmg" length="4310766" type="application/octet-stream" sparkle:edSignature="/Zel+cupZaAbA82E6PzHUiu9IVNEtoCOY61AwOZhOVHdPE+wqllywPsGyABNSTP3a+jw4FNN1HLAdNPhgJ2jAg=="/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recipe Robot 2.3.1</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 16:32:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <sparkle:version>1375</sparkle:version>
      <sparkle:shortVersionString>2.3.1</sparkle:shortVersionString>
      <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.14.6</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
      <description><![CDATA[<h3 id="fixed">Fixed</h3>

<ul>
  <li>Jamf pkg upload recipes that use a parent download recipe that retrieves a package file won’t fail (related to the behavior change below, #193).</li>
  <li>Fixed a very rare issue in which Recipe Robot is not able to remove its cache folder after a pkg is unpacked that contains files that aren’t user-writeable.</li>
  <li>Adjusted SourceForge download URL search process and updated SF RSS parsing logic. Added support for detection of SourceForge <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">/project/</code> URLs, which apparently coexist with <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">/projects/</code> URLs.</li>
  <li>Made adjustments to functional tests for upcoming AutoPkg 3 recipe map compatibility.</li>
</ul>

<h3 id="changed">Changed</h3>

<ul>
  <li>Recipe Robot no longer skips creating ‘pkg’ type recipes if the download is already in pkg format. Instead, it creates a recipe with a <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">PkgCopier</code> process (and potentially other processes if necessary for versioning). (#193)</li>
</ul>
]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://github.com/homebysix/recipe-robot/releases/download/v2.3.1/RecipeRobot-2.3.1.dmg" length="4348208" type="application/octet-stream" sparkle:edSignature="8+RnS8TiBcZBwmLVEHVI7rwD1scvZ3RGKpjrjodC4n8pzEaMOxHQZukOV2HutYGb06H0f6szAnqA8uD5KcZyDQ=="/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recipe Robot 2.3.0</title>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 14:08:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <sparkle:version>1363</sparkle:version>
      <sparkle:shortVersionString>2.3.0</sparkle:shortVersionString>
      <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.14.6</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
      <description><![CDATA[<h3 id="added">Added</h3>

<ul>
  <li>Recipe Robot is now able to create yaml recipes. To use this feature, run <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">--configure</code> and select <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">yaml</code> as the recipe format. (Or run <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">defaults write com.elliotjordan.recipe-robot RecipeFormat "yaml"</code>). The app does not yet have a method for selecting this preference.</li>
  <li>Now “jamf” recipes that leverage Graham Pugh’s JamfPackageUploader processor can be created. This feature is currently limited to package-upload-only type recipes. (No creation of groups, policies, scripts, or other objects.) (#187)</li>
  <li>Redeveloped existing recipe detection using the automated AutoPkg <a href="https://github.com/autopkg/index">recipe index</a>. Recipe Robot will use this method until the <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">autopkg search</code> results become reliable again.</li>
  <li>Local <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">file://</code> URLs are now supported input paths (but be aware that these may not be desirable for providing ongoing updates via AutoPkg, unless you have automation updating the local file).</li>
  <li>New dedicated handler for Bare Bones update feeds, which are similar to Sparkle feeds but not the same. (#194)</li>
  <li>Added three more app description sources, increasing the chance that Recipe Robot will pre-fill your Munki or Jamf recipes with useful descriptions for you to customize.</li>
  <li>Added more post-recipe-creation affirmations, because why not.</li>
</ul>

<h3 id="fixed">Fixed</h3>

<ul>
  <li>Better handling of disk images that contain packages. (#188)</li>
  <li>Recipe Robot better handles downloaded payloads that contain the contents of an app bundle, but lack the enclosing bundle itself. (Thanks to @andrewzierkel for #195)</li>
  <li>Prevented app window from expanding too much horizontally when processing extremely long filename or URL inputs.</li>
  <li>Fixed incorrect <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">[0m</code> that terminated script output in app.</li>
  <li>Fixed MacUpdate description pattern matching.</li>
  <li>Better handling of URLs with unquoted spaces. (#197)</li>
  <li>Improved detection of less obvious Sparkle feeds that might at first glance appear to be download URLs.</li>
  <li>More gracefully handle Sparkle and Bare Bones feeds with no usable items or enclosure URLs.</li>
</ul>

<h3 id="changed">Changed</h3>

<ul>
  <li>Recipe Robot app finally supports dark mode in script output box!</li>
  <li>Updated <a href="https://github.com/sparkle-project/Sparkle/">Sparkle</a> framework to 2.5.1.</li>
  <li>If existing recipes are found, output a hint that using <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">--ignore-existing</code> can create new recipes anyway.</li>
  <li>Use zero-width space for script output contents placeholder, which ensures that “Processing” on the first line aligns with the left side.</li>
</ul>

<h3 id="removed">Removed</h3>

<ul>
  <li>Removed support for generation of “jss” style recipes, which leverage the deprecated <a href="https://github.com/jssimporter/python-jss">Python-JSS</a> module. Please <a href="https://grahamrpugh.com/2022/02/16/jssimporter-jamf-pro-api-token-auth.html">switch to JamfUploader type recipes</a> instead.</li>
  <li>Dropped AlternativeTo as a description source.</li>
</ul>

<h3 id="known-issues">Known issues</h3>

<ul>
  <li>The old Sparkle feed automation needs some adjustment, so users of Recipe Robot 2.2.0 may see an incorrect “you’re up to date” message when checking for updates. Current workaround is to manually download and install version 2.3.0.</li>
</ul>
]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://github.com/homebysix/recipe-robot/releases/download/v2.3.0/RecipeRobot-2.3.0.dmg" length="4333105" type="application/octet-stream" sparkle:edSignature="7AuqOqyVK8dqrUmjESF+UgLnybcesla80TLtAvUKT5KrcBgUuFInDXkNxakz+UFRkBV20xI0qWIuFruHGmDVDw=="/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recipe Robot 2.2.0</title>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 06:35:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <sparkle:version>1291</sparkle:version>
      <sparkle:shortVersionString>2.2.0</sparkle:shortVersionString>
      <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.13</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
      <description><![CDATA[<h3 id="added">Added</h3>

<ul>
  <li>Recipe Robot now incorporates <a href="https://sparkle-project.org">Sparkle</a> for keeping itself up to date. (#143)</li>
  <li>The app is now built as a universal binary (however no testing on Macs with Apple Silicon has been done yet).</li>
  <li>Verbose output now includes HTTP content-type and copying from disk images.</li>
</ul>

<h3 id="fixed">Fixed</h3>

<ul>
  <li>Improved code signing authorities parsing, which should allow Recipe Robot to capture developer names and team identifiers in some situations where it would not previously.</li>
  <li>Fixed a bug that would prevent using Sparkle URLs hosted on updates.devmate.com as input.</li>
  <li>Gracefully handle missing file errors during installer payload inspection.</li>
  <li>Slightly more resilient processing of downloaded files when the file format is unknown.</li>
</ul>

<h3 id="removed">Removed</h3>

<ul>
  <li>Removed FoundationPlist since Recipe Robot no longer depends on it.</li>
</ul>
]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://github.com/homebysix/recipe-robot/releases/download/v2.2.0/RecipeRobot-2.2.0.dmg" length="9181288" type="application/octet-stream"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recipe Robot 2.1.0</title>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 03:49:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <sparkle:version>1228</sparkle:version>
      <sparkle:shortVersionString>2.1.0</sparkle:shortVersionString>
      <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.13</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
      <description><![CDATA[<h3 id="added">Added</h3>
<ul>
  <li>Recipe Robot is now codesigned with a shiny new developer certificate and notarized!</li>
  <li>Unit tests for <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">curl</code> related functions that will help detect and prevent release of bugs.</li>
</ul>

<h3 id="fixed">Fixed</h3>
<ul>
  <li>Fixed a bug that would fail recipe generation if a <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">expected_authority_names</code> list is used for <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">CodeSignatureVerifier</code>.</li>
  <li>Resolved an uncaught exception resulting from the <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">RecipeIdentifierPrefix</code> or <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">RecipeCreateLocation</code> preferences being unset. (#179)</li>
  <li>Corrected minimum system version back to 10.13. (#180)</li>
</ul>
]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://github.com/homebysix/recipe-robot/releases/download/v2.1.0/RecipeRobot-2.1.0.dmg" length="7311881" type="application/octet-stream"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recipe Robot 2.0.0</title>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2020 22:46:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <sparkle:version>1221</sparkle:version>
      <sparkle:shortVersionString>2.0.0</sparkle:shortVersionString>
      <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.15</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
      <description><![CDATA[<h3 id="added">Added</h3>
<ul>
  <li>Full Python 3 support, which makes Recipe Robot compatible with (and require) AutoPkg 2. Big thanks to <a href="https://github.com/sheagcraig">@sheagcraig</a> for fixing a particularly sticky bug involving string encoding. (#156, #160, #163)</li>
  <li>As part of Python 3 transition, rewrote significant portions of Recipe Robot to use <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">curl</code> instead of Python’s urllib. This adds flexibility and mimics AutoPkg’s behavior, but may result in changes in behavior from Recipe Robot 1.x.</li>
  <li>New disk image build tool and layout.</li>
  <li>The <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">recipe-robot</code> script now supports the creation of “jss-upload” type recipes, which imports a package into Jamf Pro but does not create any policies or groups. (#153)</li>
  <li>Now able to build recipes for macOS screen saver (.saver) bundles.</li>
  <li>Recipe Robot now does more thorough pre-checking of URLs: attempts to use HTTPS instead of HTTP when possible, and tries to add a widely used user-agent if a 403 error is encountered.</li>
  <li>Added CodeQL scanning to GitHub repo.</li>
  <li>Added Sparkle shortVersionString to verbose output. (#173)</li>
  <li>Added code signature team identifier verbose output. (#174)</li>
</ul>

<h3 id="changed">Changed</h3>
<ul>
  <li>Recipe Robot no longer assigns AutoPkg input variables for <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">DOWNLOAD_URL</code>, <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">SPARKLE_FEED_URL</code>, <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">GITHUB_REPO</code>, and <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">BUNDLE_ID</code>. Instead, it hard-codes these values into the appropriate processor arguments. <a href="https://github.com/jazzace">@jazzace</a> nicely summarizes the benefit of this change <a href="https://youtu.be/BI10WWrgG2A?t=2620">here</a>.</li>
  <li>Added detail to the <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">--configure</code> option that clarifies that following the official “jss-recipes” style format is unnecessary unless you’re contributing to <a href="https://www.github.com/autopkg/jss-recipes">jss-recipes</a>.</li>
  <li>Recipe Robot script <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">--configure</code> option now treats pressing Return the same as pressing “S” to save the list of preferred recipe types, to align with the behavior of other configuration options.</li>
  <li>Various minor adjustments to continue preparing for Python 3 compatibility.</li>
  <li>Cleaned up Swift codebase using <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">swiftlint</code>.</li>
  <li>More robust Sparkle feed processing. (#150, #173)</li>
</ul>

<h3 id="fixed">Fixed</h3>
<ul>
  <li>Resolved an issue that resulted in preferences unrelated to Recipe Robot being saved into the Recipe Robot preference file.</li>
  <li>Updated regular expression used to grab app descriptions from MacUpdate.</li>
  <li>Fixed an issue that would cause certain GitHub URLs to be parsed incorrectly.</li>
  <li>Fixed a bug that occurred when checking for existing recipes using AutoPkg 2. (#171)</li>
  <li>Resolved a first-run issue with reading empty preference values.</li>
  <li>Fixed an issue that could cause a disk to fill up with recursive links. (#158)</li>
  <li>Caught an error that resulted from neglecting to cast certain lists before writing to recipe plist.</li>
  <li>Better handle download file inputs that are lacking <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">kMDItemWhereFroms</code> extended attributes.</li>
  <li>Worked around an issue preventing real-time script output from being displayed in the app by shelling out to <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">echo</code> while running in app mode. (#169, #170)</li>
</ul>

<h3 id="removed">Removed</h3>
<ul>
  <li>Removed internal support for piped subprocess commands, previously deprecated in v1.2.0.</li>
  <li>Temporarily removed 403 error detection (usually due to rate-limiting) for BitBucket, GitHub, and SourceForge API calls.</li>
  <li>Removed all calls to FoundationPlist in support of Python 3 transition. (Left FoundationPlist itself included in source, but will remove in a future release.)</li>
</ul>

<h3 id="known-issues">Known Issues</h3>
<ul>
  <li>On macOS 10.14 (and possibly earlier) an incorrect “certificate has expired” warning may appear in the output. (#165)</li>
  <li>The “jss-upload” type is not addressable yet in the Recipe Robot app, only in the script.</li>
  <li>Because Recipe Robot is now using plistlib instead of FoundationPlist, it’s likely that some non-standard developer plist files may not successfully parse. This is because plistlib is stricter than FoundationPlist, and the same issue applies to AutoPkg itself (see <a href="https://github.com/autopkg/autopkg/issues/618">autopkg#618</a> for an example).</li>
</ul>
]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://github.com/homebysix/recipe-robot/releases/download/v2.0.0/RecipeRobot-2.0.0.dmg" length="14974392" type="application/octet-stream"/>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
